chicagojournal.com 2001-04-13

# E*PRAIRIE.COM - Midwest Technology Business News

**Privacy Statement for ePrairie.com:**  
ePrairie.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for ePrairie.com. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. 

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary and shared with other companies who may want to contact our visitors. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data for other purposes. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

This site contains links to other sites. ePrairie.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information about our company, and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary and shared with other companies who may want to contact our visitors. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary and shared with other companies who may want to contact our visitors. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary and shared with other companies who may want to contact our visitors. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies. 

**Public Forums:**  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. NO ONE UNDER THE AGE OF THIRTEEN IS ALLOWED TO POST ANYTHING TO ANY OF THESE FEATURES. 

**Children's Guidelines:**  
NO ONE UNDER THE AGE OF THIRTEEN IS ALLOWED TO REGISTER OR POST ANY INFORMATION ON EPRAIRIE.COM 

Users that are over the age of 12 but are under the age of 18 are permitted to register and participate, however publication of contest winner information will require parental or legal guardian consent. If consent is not given, the contract will be deemed voided and a new winner will be selected. We at ePrairie.com caution anyone under the age of 18 to be very careful to not submit personal information that you do not want the general public to view 

**Choice/Opt-Out:**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.  
You can send email to [info@eprairie.com](mailto:info@eprairie.com)  
You can visit the following URL: <http://eprairie.com/optout/>

**Correct/Update:**  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.  
Email: [info@eprairie.com](mailto:info@eprairie.com)  

**Contacting the Web Site:**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact [copyright@eprairie.com](mailto:copyright@eprairie.com).
